So what do we need to do to make lookup faster?
那么 我们需要做什么来使查找更快呢？
Well let's think about why it was so slow, right? The reason
嗯 让我们想想为什么它这么慢吧
it was so slow is that we were doing this for loop,
它这么慢的原因是 我们用循环来查找
we were going through all the elements in order, and we're checking
我们按顺序遍历所有的元素并且检查
if they match the keyword, right? And we had to do this going through
它们是否与关键字匹配 对吧？而且我们不得不遍历
the entire index, for an entry, for a keyword that's not
整个索引 来查找一个条目 查找一个索引中不存在
in the index, to determine that it's not there, we had to
的关键字 为了确定它不存在 我们不得不
go through the whole index. This is not the way we use indexes
遍历整个索引 这不是我们在现实生活中
in real life, right? If you're looking for a word in the
使用索引的方式 如果你要在一本书的索引中
index of a book, you don't have to look through every single entry
查找一个词 你不必将每一个条目都看一遍
to see if that word exists. You can jump around, and the
来确定这次词是否存在 你可以跳跃浏览
reason that you can jump around is because the entries in the index,
你能跳跃浏览的原因是在索引中的条目都是
are sorted, they're sorted in alphabetical order, so you know where that
分类排序的 它们按字母顺序排序 使你得知这个条目
entry would belong. You just need to find the right place and see
属于哪部分 你只需要找到对应的部分看看
if it's there. So we can do that with our index instead
它是否存在 因此 我们可以使用
of having our index kept in arbitrary order. If we kept our index
不随意排序的索引来做到这一点 如果我们使索引保持
in assorted order, then we could find the place where
分类排序 那么我们就能找到条目所属
that entry belongs and look for it. Sorting is a very
的位置并找到它 排序是一个非常
interesting problem. It's something we're not actually going to talk about more
有趣的问题 这些内容实际上我们不会在本课程
in this class. We're going to do a different way of doing
讨论太多 我们要用一种不同的方式来
that. What we're going to do is find a way to
操作 我们现在要做的是找到一种方法
find where the entry should be that doesn't require actually keeping
来找到条目应该在哪里 而实际上并不需要使
all the entries sorted. What we want is something that will
所有条目保持排序 我们要做到的是可以
allow us, given a keyword, we're going to have some function that
使我们做到 给定一个关键字 将有一些函数
tells us where it belongs. We're going to call that
告诉我们它属于哪里 我们将称之为
a hash function. That tells us where in the entry
哈希函数 它会告诉我们条目在哪里
to look. And so instead of having to look through
查看 所以不必遍历
the whole index, the hash function will tell us where
整个索引 哈希函数会告诉我们该条目
that entry belongs. So what we need for this is
所属位置 所以我们需要的是
some function that's going to take a key word, map
一些函数 传入一个关键字 以一个数字
it to a number And that number is the position
定位它 这个数字是该条目在
in the index where that number belongs. We could do this
索引中的位置 我们可以用
lots of different ways. One simple thing would be to
许多不同的方式做到这一点 其中一个简单的方式是
think, well we know alphabet. This is more like the way
想想 我们知道字母表 这更像是
an index for a book would work, and we're going to
书本索引的工作方式 然后我们要
have for each entry and index, we'll have based on the
根据首字母 给每个条目一个下标
first letter, we'll put all the entries that start with
我们会把所有首字母相同
that first letter in the same place. So, if we're looking
的项放在相同的位置 所以 如果我们寻找
for a keyword that starts with u, that prefer hash
以 U 开头的关键字 这个哈希
would tell us to look in the place where all the
会告诉我们去所有以 U 开头的词
words that start with u are. And then we'd only have to
所在的位置寻找 然后我们就只需要
look through the words that start with u. So this would allow
遍历所有以 U 开头的词 那么这将使得
us to do a look up much more quickly than looking through
我们一次查找的速度远远超过遍历
the whole index. This isn't quite the best way to do things. If
整个索引 这并不是最好的方式 如果
we made our places based on the letter, well, then we have
我们根据字母分好区 那么我们就会有
a problem if we have two words with the same first letter. You
一个问题 如果我们有两个首字母相同的单词 你
generally expect to have more than one word that starts with the
通常都会有多个单词的首字母相同
same letter. So instead of having just an element here for each position,
因此 不是每个位置只有一个元素
we're going to have a list of elements that would be all
我们将有一个列表 包括所有
the words that start with u So when we look up the
以 U 开头的单词 所以当我们查找
word udacity, we look in the entry for u, and if the
udacity 我们查找 U 列表中的条目 如果
word that's there doesn't match then we know udacity isn't in the
该词未找到匹配项 那么我们就知道 udacity 不在
index. There are lots of problems with this. The first problem is
索引中 这其中有很多问题 第一个问题是
well, there might be more than one word that starts with u.
嗯 可能有不止一个词的首字母为 U
So we can't just have one entry here. What we need to
所以我们在这里不能只有一个条目 我们需要的是
have is a list of entries We often call this a bucket.
有一整个列表的条目 我们常常称之为 桶 (bucket)
So we need a bucket of all the entries that
那么 我们需要一个所有条目的桶 (bucket)
start with u that would be in this position. So, instead
在这个以 U 开头的位置 因此
of just having one entry like the old structure of our
不像我们旧索引结构一样 只有一个
index, now we're going to have a list of entries, and
条目 现在我们将拥有一个条目列表 而且
each element of the index will now be a bucket, which
现在 索引中的每个元素将是一个桶 即
is a list of entries that are in the right position.
在正确的位置上的条目的列表
This is going to be our bucket of our, all the entries
这将是我们的所有首字母为 U 的
that start with u, and that would have all the different
条目的桶 而且其中将有所有不同的
entries that start with the letter u in that bucket. So this
以字母 U 开头的条目 那么这样
is getting better. Now, for each look up, instead of having to
变的好点了 现在 对于每个查找 不必
look through all of the words in index, we just need to
遍历所有索引的词汇 我们只需要
find the position that starts with the right letter. That's got a
找到正确首字母的位置 这里找到一个
bucket of all the words that start with that letter, and then
装有所有以该字母开始的词的桶  然后
we just need to look through that bucket. This works okay, but
遍历这个桶 这样做还可以 但是
this doesn't really scale very well. At best, if we have you
这并不能真正很好地缩小规模 最好的情况 如果你
know, ten million words well now instead of having ten million entries
知道的话 1000万字现在不必遍历1000万个
to go through, we need to go through ten million divided
条目 而是遍历1000万除以 26
by say 26, if we have 26 letters. It's not making
如果我们有26个字母 这并不能使
things much faster. It's making things maybe at best, 26 times
速度快很多 它最多也就可以处理26倍
letter. That assumes that all of the buckets are the same size.
的词 这还要假设所有的桶大小相同
Certainly if we make the buckets based on the first letter,
当然 如果我们根据首字母划分桶
that's not going to be the same size. If the words
它们不会是相同大小 如果词
are a typical English words. We're going to have many more
是典型的英语单词 我们将有更多
words that start with s or t, say than start with u.
s 或 t 开头的单词 比起以 u 开头的单词来说
So, we want to fix those two problems. We want to
所以 我们要解决这些两个问题 我们想要
be able to have more buckets. So we're not going to just
有更多的桶 因此 我们不打算只
use the first letter, we're going to use some function on the
使用首字母 我们要对整个词使用一些函数
whole word that tells us where it belongs. And we're going to try
使它告诉我们它属于什么位置 而且我们将努力
to make that function distribute the words fairly well. So the
使该函数可以相当好得分配词语
structure that I've described is what's called a hash table. This
我所描述的结构就是所谓的哈希表
is a very useful data structure. It's so useful that it's
这是一种非常有用的数据结构 所以被
built into Python. There's the Python type called a dictionary. Which provides
内置到 Python 中 有一种叫做字典的 Python 类型 提供了
this functionality. At the end of today's unit, I'll explain
此功能 在今天的单元结束后 我会解释
how the Python dictionary works, and how to use it,
Python 的字典是如何工作的 以及如何使用它
and we'll modify the search engine code to use dictionary
我们会修改搜索引擎代码 使用字典
instead of the lookup table that we built, but before
代替我们构建的查找表 但在此之前
we do that, we are going to implement it ourselves. We
我们要自己实现它 我们
are going to make sure that we understand how the hash
要确保我们了解哈希表
table works by writing all the code to do it
的工作原理 通过自己编写所有的代码
ourselves and then we'll switch to using the built-in Python type.
然后我们将切换为使用内置的 Python 格式